<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>William Yu</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/</link><description>William Yu's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>williamyuaus@gmail.com (William Yu)</managingEditor><webMaster>williamyuaus@gmail.com (William Yu)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 18:40:03 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://williamyuaus.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fix Generating Equals/hashcode Implementation but Without a Call to Superclass</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/fix-generating-equalshashcode-implementation-but-without-a-call-to-superclass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 18:40:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/fix-generating-equalshashcode-implementation-but-without-a-call-to-superclass/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202208151849632.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><h2 id="the-warning-from-building-a-spring-boot-project">The warning from building a Spring Boot project</h2>
<p>When I built my Spring boot project, I got 20 warnings about a same thing. The warning shows: <code>Generating equals/hashCode implementation but without a call to superclass</code></p>
<p></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Install Redis on OpenSUSE Leap 15.4</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/install-redis-on-opensuse-leap-15.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:23:30 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/install-redis-on-opensuse-leap-15.4/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/redis_opensuse.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>since there is no Redis official package for OpenSUSE Leap 15.4, it is difficult for us to install Redis on this Linux. I tried several ways to install Redis, including via Snap. But both of them did not work. Finally, I tried install Redis by complying from the source.
Steps for installing Redis First, we need to download Redis source package as we can find on the official website.
To obtain the source files for the latest stable version of Redis from the Redis downloads site, run:</description></item><item><title>Fix 413 Request Entity Too Large Error</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/fix-413-request-entity-too-large-error/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 14:20:09 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/fix-413-request-entity-too-large-error/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210826211757.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><p>After I deployed my web app online, when I tried to upload a PDF file to store in AWS S3 bucket, I received the 413 error as below.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Change the Language of Vue Image Crop Upload</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/change-the-language-of-vue-image-crop-upload/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 14:18:44 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/change-the-language-of-vue-image-crop-upload/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210826141533.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>For developing a user-friendly Vue app, it is essential to enable a user to upload their profile images. To have better results, the app needs to crop the images to fit the size.
For this purpose, I found a component for it. It is called vue-image-crop-upload. It is a beautiful Vue component for image crop and upload.
However, since the default language of vue-image-crop-upload is Chinese, you can only see the component with Chinese instructions as below.</description></item><item><title>How to Post an Article in WordPress</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/how-to-post-an-article-in-wordpress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 14:17:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/08/how-to-post-an-article-in-wordpress/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210813154219.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Intro If you have a personal website, or you have a website for your own business, you would like to post some news or articles to make your website more active. However, if your website is developed by others, the only thing you know is that your website is built by WordPress and your username and password. How could you post articles in your website? Now, this tutorial will guide you through the process.</description></item><item><title>How to Install Docker in AWS EC2 Instances</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/07/how-to-install-docker-in-aws-ec2-instances/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 14:15:42 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/07/how-to-install-docker-in-aws-ec2-instances/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210726104413.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Once you have created an AWS EC2 instance, you probably want to deploy your app on it using Docker. So, you might need to install Docker in the EC2 instance first.
Firstly, you need to connect to your instance via SSH. Once connected, you will see the command line in your terminal: Before installing Docker, you may need to update the installed packages and package cache on your instance. sudo yum update -y If your instance is Amazon Linux 2, using the command to install the most recent Docker Engine package.</description></item><item><title>How to Fix Add New Plugin Menu Missing in WordPress</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/07/how-to-fix-add-new-plugin-menu-missing-in-wordpress/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 14:13:24 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/07/how-to-fix-add-new-plugin-menu-missing-in-wordpress/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210708144905.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Plugins are very important for WordPress development. By default, we can add new plugin in the WordPress sidebar.
However, I just found that the &lsquo;Add new plugin menu&rsquo; is missing in my WordPress site.
The plugins can only be clicked as shown the list of installed plugins. Which means I cannot add new plugins on my site.
To fix this issue, I tried several ways. Firstly, I changed the theme to the default one.]]></description></item><item><title>How to Fix the Vue Router Link Issue</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-the-vue-router-link-issue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 14:09:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-the-vue-router-link-issue/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/20210610115342.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>The issue of the Vue router link Since I implemented The Vue Router in my application, I found an issue that is wired.
When I hovered my cursor on the button, it cannot be clicked and switch to the route page immediately. There was nothing happened. All I need to do was that I need to place the cursor out of the button, and moved it back again. At this time, the same button might be clickable and switch to the correct page.</description></item></channel></rss>