<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - William Yu</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/posts/</link><description>All Posts | William Yu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>williamyuaus@gmail.com (William Yu)</managingEditor><webMaster>williamyuaus@gmail.com (William Yu)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:59:33 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://williamyuaus.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set Up VS Code for Remote Development</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2024/02/set-up-vs-code-for-remote-development/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:59:33 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2024/02/set-up-vs-code-for-remote-development/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202402091703658.webp" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Background Remote development is crucial for many scenarios. If we have a Windows PC but need to develop our projects on Linux, remote development is the right way to go. VS Code is very easy to set up for remote development. Let&rsquo;s dive into it.
Prerequisite A virtual machine is already set up, the SSH tunnel is working between your local machine and the VM.
VS Code set up First, install the Remote - SSH extension on your VS Code.]]></description></item><item><title>Fix the Error of Null Value for Field With @Creationtimestamp</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2024/01/fix-the-error-of-null-value-for-field-with-creationtimestamp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:43:32 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2024/01/fix-the-error-of-null-value-for-field-with-creationtimestamp/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202401221050208.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Background In a Spring Boot project, an entity class has a @CreationTimestamp annotation for the field of started. Since this field is essential for our business logic, there is a NotNull restriction in the database column for it.
This is the code for this entity (Review.java):
@Entity(name = &#34;review&#34;) @EqualsAndHashCode(onlyExplicitlyIncluded = true) @TypeDef(name = &#34;jsonb&#34;, typeClass = JsonBinaryType.class) @TypeDef(name = &#34;pgsql_enum&#34;, typeClass = PostgreSQLEnumType.class) @Getter @Setter @JsonIgnoreProperties({&#34;hibernateLazyInitializer&#34;, &#34;handler&#34;}) public class Review { @Id @EqualsAndHashCode.]]></description></item><item><title>Disabling Error Notification Toast when Generating PDF from a Vue Project</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/08/disable-the-error-notification-toast-when-generating-pdf-from-a-vue-project/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:27:22 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/08/disable-the-error-notification-toast-when-generating-pdf-from-a-vue-project/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202308111307432.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Intro When generating a PDF from a webpage using Puppeteer in a Vue project, it&rsquo;s often desirable to prevent the display of any error notification popups. This was the challenge I encountered. Specifically, in a Vue project, when a REST API call failed, a notification popup would appear on the browser screen. If a PDF version of the webpage needed to be generated, this popup would persist in the output. An example of this scenario is illustrated below: Approach My solution involved utilizing a media query.]]></description></item><item><title>Potential Issues With Spring Jpa Properties You Should Avoid in Production</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/03/potential-issues-with-spring-jpa-properties-you-should-avoid-in-production/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 15:34:29 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/03/potential-issues-with-spring-jpa-properties-you-should-avoid-in-production/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202303311535597.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Introduction Java developers love the Spring Framework since it has gained immense popularity due to its simplicity, flexibility, and robustness. Spring is a powerful tool that simplifies the development of enterprise applications by providing various features and functionalities. One such feature is the Spring Data JPA, which is an abstraction over the JPA specification. Although Spring Boot provides a powerful auto-configuration feature that makes it easy to configure and set up various components of an application, misconfiguring certain properties can lead to unintended consequences and potential issues.</description></item><item><title>Increasing the Size of the Disk of VM</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/01/increasing-the-size-of-the-disk-of-vm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:22:46 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/01/increasing-the-size-of-the-disk-of-vm/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202301251519566.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Intro As we are developing more and more projects on my VM, we might get a problem which is the disk would be full. Obviously, we can clean up our file system to free up more space. However, if you got the issue frequently, it is better to increase the size of your disk for your VM.
Pre-check for your disks First of all, you need to know the status of your disks at beginning.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Website Contact Form Away From Spam</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/01/get-your-website-contact-form-away-from-spam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:20:47 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2023/01/get-your-website-contact-form-away-from-spam/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202301101024090.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>You may just finished your own website, and added a contact form and waiting for any potential customers requesting further information from you. However, few days passed, most of the email you have received are spam. Such as this:
This is one of the examples in my inbox. I got this kind of email several times per day. Later on, I&rsquo;m not excited to check the new email from the contact form.]]></description></item><item><title>Getting Started With Elasticsearch and Kibana (Opensearch)</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/10/getting-started-with-elasticsearch-and-kibana-opensearch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:30:25 +1100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/10/getting-started-with-elasticsearch-and-kibana-opensearch/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202210201632194.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>What is the OpenSearch project? The OpenSearch project, created by Amazon, is a forked search project based on old versions of Elasticsearch and Kibana. It is a 100% open-source search, analytics, and visualization suite.
Why use OpenSearch? Fast, Scalable Full-text Search Help users find the right information within your application, website, or data lake catalog.
Application and Infrastructure Monitoring Easily store and analyze log data, and set automated alerts for underperformance.</description></item><item><title>Unit Testing for Vue Router Global After Hooks</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/unit-testing-for-vue-router-global-after-hooks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 14:50:50 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/unit-testing-for-vue-router-global-after-hooks/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202208241453558.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Intro It is always not easy to do the unit testing for the Vue Router. People prefer to implement end-to-end testing for this. Especially, if you have defined some Vue router global hooks, it would be more difficult to testing the execution of them.
Fortunately, we still can find a way to do the unit testing for the Vue Router Global After Hooks
Background In my project, I have implemented afterEach as global after hooks in my Vue router settings.</description></item><item><title>Fix Generating Equals/hashcode Implementation but Without a Call to Superclass</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/fix-generating-equalshashcode-implementation-but-without-a-call-to-superclass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 18:40:03 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/fix-generating-equalshashcode-implementation-but-without-a-call-to-superclass/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/202208151849632.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div><h2 id="the-warning-from-building-a-spring-boot-project">The warning from building a Spring Boot project</h2>
<p>When I built my Spring boot project, I got 20 warnings about a same thing. The warning shows: <code>Generating equals/hashCode implementation but without a call to superclass</code></p>
<p></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Install Redis on OpenSUSE Leap 15.4</title><link>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/install-redis-on-opensuse-leap-15.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:23:30 +1000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://williamyuaus.com/2022/08/install-redis-on-opensuse-leap-15.4/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/williamyuaus/blog-img/master/img/redis_opensuse.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>since there is no Redis official package for OpenSUSE Leap 15.4, it is difficult for us to install Redis on this Linux. I tried several ways to install Redis, including via Snap. But both of them did not work. Finally, I tried install Redis by complying from the source.
Steps for installing Redis First, we need to download Redis source package as we can find on the official website.
To obtain the source files for the latest stable version of Redis from the Redis downloads site, run:</description></item></channel></rss>